Alright the drink that we are about to make is a Black and Tan.
Now there's a lot of debate on what two beers are supposed to be used for a black and tan.
But if you ask most people they'll tell you that Guinness and Bask Ale.
First thing we're going to do is we're going to take a pint glass and start by pouring in your Bask, half way.
And we're going to fill it the rest of the way with Guinness.
And the Guinness is darker.
You will see the difference in the top and the bottom.
It should have a nice distinction between that and let's get a close up so you can see.
And the top should be a little bit darker than the bottom.
And that's a Black and Tan.
So anytime you want to spice up your Guinness a little bit, and you don't feel like having just a Bask, make yourself a Black and Tan, a mixture of both.
Bottoms up.